http://www.guideddiscoveries.com/guideddiscoveries/privacy-policy/

800-645-1423
CareersSee Us in Action HomeAbout UsHistoryMeet Our TeamFinancialsTestimonialsPress and MediaEducation Through ExplorationGuided Discoveries MissionTeaching PhilosophyPartners in LearningResearch and DevelopmentSchool ProgramsCatalina Island Marine InstituteAstroCampSummer CampsCatalina Sea CampAstroCampCamp MotorSportGiving and DonationsWish ListFinancial Aid FundEventsHow You Can HelpAlumni AssociationStoreContact Information What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register for camp or manage your camper account, respond to a survey, fill out a form or request information on our programs.When requesting information on our programs you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.When registering a child for camp or maintaining your camper account, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, date of birth, emergency contact information, and medical information.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you); To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature; To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?We do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on April 9, 2012Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.www.guideddiscoveries.org P. O. Box 1360 Claremont, California 91711-1360 USA webmaster@guideddiscoveries.orgQuick LinksAdministratorsNew EmployeesGet Connected
©Guided Discoveries, All Rights Reserved 2014 | Privacy PolicyContact UsGuided Discoveries,27282 Calle ArroyoSan Juan Capistrano, CA 92675Phone: 800-645-1423Fax: 909-625-7305Email: info@gdi.org Learn About Skunkworks
